viceroyhotelsandresorts.com 2011-01-14

# Viceroy Hotels Privacy and Security: Luxury Resorts in Southern California, the Caribbean and More

### Our Privacy Policy and Security Statement

We want viceroyhotelsandresorts.com (hereinafter all identified URLs are collectively referred to as the "Website" or "Websites") visitors to feel confident about using our Site to plan and purchase their accommodations, so we are committed to protecting the information we collect. All personal information you provide is encrypted and secure.

At Viceroy Hotels and Resorts in Southern California, the Caribbean, Miami and Snowmass, the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information is important. We are committed to maintaining the privacy and security of your personal information. We may update this policy from time to time, so please check here frequently. We will not disclose identifiable user information to any third party without your consent.

Viceroy Hotels and Resorts is committed to safeguarding your privacy while visiting our Miami, Palm Springs, Anguilla, Snowmass and Santa Monica hotel Websites including viceroyhotelsandresorts.com. Our goal is to provide you with an Internet experience that delivers the information, resources and services that are most relevant to you. To achieve this goal, part of the operation of our Websites includes the gathering of certain types of information about our Website visitor.

We understand that your privacy is important, we wish to explain the types of information we gather and the way in which we use it. This Privacy Policy applies to the viceroyhotelsandresorts.com and the entire viceroyhotelgroup.com website. This Privacy Policy covers two types of information gathered on our Websites, personal and aggregated. The term "personal information" refers to data you voluntarily provide in connection with use of our Websites that identifies you and/or the company on whose behalf you are accessing and using our Websites. Personal information includes, e.g., data submitted in connection with our services, such as your name, e-mail address, phone number, company affiliation, physical address and/or certain other personal information. The term "aggregated data" refers to general information regarding visitors and users of our Websites’ features of our Website or other parties made available through or found on our Websites.

### What information is collected about you? How do we use it?

We take the utmost care to ensure that the personal information we obtain from you is not used in a way that you may be unaware of or not agreeable to. You may wish to submit an information request about our hotel, participate in one of our promotions or subscribe to our e-mail or postal mail lists. In response, we may ask for information such as your name and postal address. In the event you opt to provide us with this information, we will only use it for the purpose specified by you at the bottom of the information gathering form.

### Information collected on our Websites may be used to:

  * Register you as a viceroyhotelsandresorts.com member
  * Plan and purchase hotel accommodations 
  * Enter you in promotions or sweepstakes 
  * Send marketing communications or surveys to you 
  * Respond to your questions or suggestions 
  * Improve the quality of your visit to our site 

All forms will provide an opt-out button to allow you to choose not to participate in our hotel lists and future online marketing. In deciding whether or not to join such lists, please note that they are only used for hotel purposes or in joint promotions with a hotel partner. We do not sell, rent or share any of your personal information with any other party including any third-party joint promoters, nor use it for unapproved commercial purposes. You may request to be removed from our lists at any time. All emails distributed to our lists will contain easy, online access to unsubscribe.

### Permission for Use

We may collect and use personal information that you submit to our Websites in any manner that is consistent with uses stated in this Privacy Policy or disclosed elsewhere at the Website at the point you submit such personal information. At the time you submit personal information or make a request, the intended use of the information you submit will be apparent in the context in which you submit it and/or because the Website states the intended purpose. By submitting personal information on our Websites, you are giving your consent and permission for any use that is consistent with uses stated in this Privacy Policy or disclosed elsewhere at the Website at the point you submit such personal information, and such consent will be presumed by our hotel, unless you state otherwise at the time you submit the personal information. Please do not request any such communications on behalf of an individual or company if you are not authorized to make the request.

### Secure Reservations

If you decide to make an online reservation on our Website, you will be linked to a reservation interface and a third-party booking engine provided by Synxis. While it appears to be part of our Website, the Booking Engine is in fact provided by a third party and is governed by its privacy practices. We understand that security remains the primary concern of online consumers and have chosen the Booking Engine Vendor carefully. The Booking Engine Vendor participates in the VeriSign Secure Website Program, a top security certification program, and:

  * Has a VeriSign Secure Server ID. 
  * All information sent to this Website, if in an SSL session, is encrypted, protecting against disclosure to third parties. 

### Protecting your information

We would like our Website visitors to feel confident about planning and purchasing your accommodations online, so we are committed to protecting the information we collect. We've implemented a security program to keep information that is stored in our systems protected from unauthorized access. Our Website is hosted in a secure environment. The Website servers and systems are configured with data encryption technologies and industry-standard firewalls. When you enter personal information during the reservation process, or during a customer email sign-up, your data is protected by Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure safe transmission.

### Withdrawing Consent to Use

If, after permitting use of your personal information, you later decide that you no longer want our hotel to include you on its mailing list or otherwise contact you or use your personal information in the manner disclosed in this Privacy Policy or on our Website, simply click on the "Unsubscribe" button at the bottom of our email communication to you.

### Use of Aggregated Data

We are interested in improving our Website and may develop and offer new features and services. We monitor aggregated data regarding use of our Website for marketing purposes and to study, improve and promote use of the Website in connection with such purposes. We may share aggregated data with third parties collectively and in an anonymous way. Disclosure of aggregated data does not reveal personal information about individual Website users in any way that identifies who they are or how to contact them.

### Exceptions to the Privacy Policy

We have two exceptions to these limits on use of personal information:

  * We may monitor and, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is required, disclose information to protect the security, property, assets and/or rights of our Website from unauthorized use, or misuse, of our Website or anything found on our Website. 
  * We may disclose information when required by law; however, only to the extent necessary and in a manner that seeks to maintain the privacy of the individual. 

### Use of Cookies

To enable features on our Website, we may assign one or more "cookies" to your Internet browser. Cookies, among other things, speed navigation through our Website, keep track of information so that you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our Website, and may provide you with customized content. A cookie is an Internet mechanism composed of a small text file containing a unique identification number that permits a web server to send small pieces of information or text by means of your browser and place them on your computer's hard drive for storage. This text lets the web server know if you have previously visited our website. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user.

We use cookies to collect and maintain aggregated data (such as the number of visitors) to help us see which areas are most popular with our users and improve and update the content on our Website. While in the process of browsing our Website, you also provide us with information that doesn't reveal your personal identity -- what type of destination you're exploring, for example. We use this aggregated data only as explained in this Privacy Policy. We do not connect aggregated data to any name, address, or other identifying information.

You may occasionally receive cookies from unaffiliated companies or organizations, to the extent they place advertising on our Website or are linked to our Website. These third-party cookies may collect information about you when you "click" on their advertising or content or link. This practice is standard in the Internet industry. Because of the way in which the Internet operates, we cannot control collection of this information by these third parties, and these cookies are not subject to this Privacy Policy.

### Children's Privacy & Parental Consent

Please be aware that our hotel company has not designed this Website for, and does not intend for it to be used by, anyone under age 18. Accordingly, this Website should not be used by anyone under age 18. Our privacy policy prohibits us from accepting users who are under the age of 18. We specifically request that persons under the age of 18 not use this Website or submit or post information to the Website. Should we inadvertently acquire personal information or other data from users under the age of 18, we will not knowingly provide this data to any third party for any purpose whatsoever, and any subsequent disclosure would be due to the fact the user under age 18 used our Website and submitted personal information without solicitation by or permission from us.

### Links Provided To Other Websites

We may provide links to a number of other Websites that we believe might offer you useful information and services. However, those Websites may not follow the same privacy policies as our hotel. Therefore, we are not responsible for the privacy policies or the actions of any third parties, including without limitation, any Website owners whose Websites may be reached through this Website, nor can we control the activities of those Websites. We urge you to contact the relevant parties controlling these Websites or accessing their on-line policies for the relevant information about their data collection practices before submitting any personal information or other sensitive data.

### Your Consent To This Privacy Policy

Use of our Website signifies your consent, as well as the consent of the company for whom you use our Website and whose information you submit (if any), to this on-line Privacy Policy, including the collection and use of information by our Website, as described in this statement, and also signifies agreement to the terms of use for the Website. Continued access and use of our Website without acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy relieves us from responsibility to the user.

### Policy Modifications & Contacting Us

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time; notice of changes will be published on this page. Changes will always be prospective, not retroactive. If you have questions about our policies, please contact:

Viceroy Hotel and Resorts   
1212 South Flower Street  
Los Angeles California 90015  
T +1 323 930 3700  
F +1 323 930 3701
